

MAHIMA MAHAJAN

DATA ANALYST
FRONT END DEVELOPER
PYTHON/R

PROFILE

My name is Mahima Mahajan. I am from Madhya Pradesh. I am in my final year of my graduation course in B-Tech CSE pursuing from D.Y. Patil International University, Akurdi, Pune. My specialization subject is focused on Data Science but have other interests such as UI Design, Cyber Security and Fronted Development. As a computer science student, I have good problem-solving skills as well as hands on practice in various technical fields and tools.

EXPERIENCE

DATA ANNOTATION (AI/ML)

STRATA UNISON (New York) I Apr 2022

2022 - Present

• During the internship the responsibility is to perform data annotation on the given dataset that are going to be used to train machine [earning model.

WEB DEVELOPMENT

TECTIQ TECHNOLOGY

May 2019 -June 2019

- worked on a project received from company.
- Responsibility to manage database and build website design.

CAMPUS AMBASSADOR

NEO EDUCATIONAL FOUNDATION

Apr 2021 - May 2021

• Spreading awareness about the National Engineering Olympiad exam with the help of different social media platforms.

ACTIVITY

- State Level Students Convention (TECHWIZARD 2.0)
- TANTROTSAV 2K19

7709842561

mahimamahajan0906@gmail.com

2 Pune, Maharashtra

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahima09

EDUCATION

DIPLOMA- COMPUTER SCIENCE

Y. B. Patil College of Engineering

2018 - 2020

B-TECH COMPUTER SCIENCE

D. Y. Patil International University2020 - 2023

PROJECTS

TARGETED ADVERTISMENT & MARKETING ANALYTICS

Performed ML techniques on the dummy dataset where the model will suggest the ads based on the interest and spending times on Instagram reels

LIBRARY

Developed a library website based on the concept of DBMS which performs simple functions like storing the books and records of books issued and many more.

DATA ANALYSIS/ ML ALGORITHM

Performed various statistical operation and exploratory data analysis on the dataset. Also, used various techniques and steps from data pre-processing to build model developing to predict the outcomes.

SKILLS

- Data Analyst
- Data Visualization
- Power BI/Excel
- UI & UX Design
- Python/C/C++/R
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Front-End Developer

HTML / CSS / PHP.

• MySQL / Databases